newair.com 2019-03-07

# Privacy Policy – NewAir

NewAir is dedicated to providing a safe purchasing environment for those that visit our website. To assure you of your privacy, we provide this notice to help you understand our commitment to security. By visiting NewAir.com, you are accepting the practices described in the Privacy Policy.

### Your Personal Information

When you provide NewAir with your personal information such as phone number or e-mail address, we will use it only for the purpose for which it was provided and can be used to send you occasional marketing messages via email. You are free to opt-out of these marketing messages using the Unsubscribe link in our email messages. We do not sell, rent, trade, or barter customer information without prior permission.

In order to submit User Generated Content, you will have to create an account with the PowerReviews network. During the course of creating an account, you may be asked to submit information, such as but not limited to, your name, email address, mailing address or phone number, and other data. The Consumer Account Info may be collected by both PowerReviews and NewAir. PowerReviews uses Consumer Account Info to assist with the creation of an account, provide you the ability to review, comment on or rate products.

### Cookies & Other Technologies

The PowerReviews network uses web beacons and other technologies to collect information from Consumers. Their technologies may collect the IP address of your computer, the pages you visit within the PowerReviews Network, the date and time of your visit, browser type and version and other click-stream data (collectively "Analytics and Tracking Data"). They use the Analytics and Tracking Data to operate the Services, enable the submission of User Generated Content, to enable anonymous analytics and measurement reporting.

### Safeguards

We utilize appropriate physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to help protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of any information you may provide at our site. We use industry-standard, 128-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption technologies when transferring and receiving customer data.

### Advertising

We occasionally utilize advertising services from sites like Google. Here's how these services may affect you:

  * Third party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites on the internet.
  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website.

You may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page.

We may modify our privacy policy any given time, therefore its important to view them regularly. NewAir also welcomes your comments regarding our Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or comments, please do not hesitate to contact us.
